When I woke up, I was riding in a flower carriage
Saat aku terbangun, aku sedang menaiki Gerobak Bunga.
It was... It was my birthday
Itu ... hari ulang tahunku.
The Knight of Flowers and their attendants found me
Kesatria Bunga dan para pengawalnya menemukanku.
"Archon, we finally found you. The people can't wait to meet you"
"Archon, akhirnya kami menemukanmu,
As the Sabzeruz Festival began, everyone smiled and gathered around me...
Festival Sabzeruz sudah dimulai, semua orang mengelilingiku sambil tersenyum gembira ....
Are those... Padisarahs?
Itu ... Padisarah?
Everyone prepared a bunch of surprises for me
Semua orang menyiapkan banyak kejutan untukku.
Candy exploded in all directions, like dazzling fireworks
Permen bertebaran ke segala arah seperti kembang api yang mekar.
Ready! Three, two, one...!
Siap! Tiga, dua, satu ...!
A bird suddenly appeared
Lalu tiba-tiba muncullah seekor burung,
And in that moment, the world erupted in brilliant color
dan pada saat itulah, dunia diliputi dengan warna-warni yang cerah,
Actually... I have a surprise of my own
Sebenarnya ... aku sendiri juga punya kejutan buat kalian semua.
Come on out!
Ayo keluarlah!
When I woke up, I was riding in a flower carriage
Saat aku terbangun, aku sedang menaiki Gerobak Bunga.
It felt just like a dream
Semua rasanya bagaikan mimpi,
Never had I witnessed a more perfect day
Rasanya itu adalah hari paling sempurna dalam hidupku.